usatestprep.com 2019-07-03

# USATestprep, LLC Privacy Policy

USATestprep, LLC Privacy Policy

USATestprep, LLC (USATestprep) is committed to protecting the privacy of our customer's personal information. In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), all personal information submitted by student and teacher Customers for use on the USATestprep website is for educational purposes only and not retained by USATestprep beyond the time necessary to provide services.USATestprep will not trade, sell or share any personal contact information entered on our site with any outside organization. This applies with respect to the information that we collect from the company web site, located at www.usatestprep.com. Approved amendments to this statement will be delivered to subscribers via internal notification prior to being posted at this URL and will become effective once posted. The absence of written disagreements from subscribers about these intended changes and their continued use of this site following the notice of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute acceptance thereof.

I. INFORMATION COLLECTED

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you by tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a survey or registration form. The types of information that may be requested include First and Last Name and Grade (required), email Address (optional), and Student Identification Number (optional). This personal information is collected in one of three ways - either by direct student entry into the USATestprep account page, or by bulk upload of information provided by an individual school or school district.

II. USE OF INFORMATION

Data is retained only for education purposes. In general, we will only use the information you provide to us for the purpose for which such information was provided. This personal information is used solely for the recording and tracking of student results on assessment items within the USATestprep, LLC website and can be accessed only by the individual student and his/her teachers or administrators at his/her school or district level. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings from us by following the instructions set forth in the opt-out section below.

Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in.

Personal information submitted by student and teacher users for use on the USATestprep website is not retained by USATestprep beyond the time necessary to provide services.

III. USE OF IP ADDRESSES

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

IV. USE OF COOKIES

When you view our web site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive or steal information. Rather, they help you navigate our web site as easily as possible. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from re-entering all of your registration data at each connection.

V. PARENTAL RIGHTS

USATestprep, LLC requires only the collection of the first and last name and grade of each student. The only other personal information requested by USATestprep, LLC is the student ID Number and Email; this information is optional and site usage is fully functional with or without this information. Schools or districts may require this information for tracking purposes. Each piece of requested information is required for participation in online assessment activities. The parent/guardian of each child is capable of reviewing their child's personal information with the use of the student's username and password. Parents/Guardians also have the ability to direct USATestprep, LLC to delete their child's personal information or to instruct USATestprep, LLC to cease the collection or use of any of the child's personal information. For parents/guardians to request to review, delete, or refuse collection of their child's personal information, parents/guardians can contact USATestprep, LLC with this request via phone, email, fax, or mail.

VI. SECURITY

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.

VII. OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS

Our Web site contains links to other web sites. USATestprep, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

VIII. CORRECT; UPDATE

USATestprep, LLC allows its users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods:

(1) e-mail the information to info@usatestprep.com

(2) call 1-877-377-9537

IX. CHOICE; OPT OUT

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us by the following means:

(1) send an e-mail to info@usatestprep.com

(2) call 1-877-377-9537.

X. SUCCESSION

In the event of the sale of the company, successor entities remain bound to the processes and policies defined in this Privacy Policy document.

Contacting us:

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at info@usatestprep.com.
